2559 Altos Ave. Sacramento, CA 95815

**Tel**: 707-951-8448

Email: triathao@gmail.com

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills to improve and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity, reputation, and providing excellent services to clients and customers.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Truck Driver, Divine Enterprises

August 2018 - August 2020, Rocklin, CA

- Inspect company vehicle for any potential safety violation, including pre-rip and post-trip.
- Trip managing and planning to ensure arrival and delivery appointments.
- Comply with federal regulations and company policies.
- Excellent driver safety with no moving violations in the past ten years.

# Kitchen Designer, Home Depot

November 2013 - June 2017, Carmichael, CA

- Consult kitchen remodels with customers while providing excellent services.
- Design multiple layouts and drawing of kitchen floor plans in CAD 20/20 for a real 3D visual.
- Handling and managing multiple projects at a time, while communicating, scheduling, and coordinating with installers, vendors, and fabricators, for a smooth start to finish project.
- Knowledgeable of multiple cabinet lines and as well as different countertop types.
- Assist sister departments, plumbing and selling appliances.
- Lead in regional sales in multiple years.

## Technical Designer, The California Bag

August 2010 - November 2013, Los Angeles, CA

- Illustrating technical line drawings of handbags for Ed Hardy Bags, Christian Audigier Bags, and Lindsay Lohan's 6126 bags.
- Working with multiple styles in a group, includes colorways, shapes, and materials.
- Revising product samples, making sure samples are as per tech packs. Making sure handbags work properly as intended.
- Other responsibility includes making sure tech packs call outs of measurements, materials, linings, vendor labels, and packaging are accurate and precise for all three brands.

#### Trim Graphic Designer, BCBGMAXAZRIA

January 2008 - August 2010, Los Angeles, CA

- Work with Designers and Creative Director, creating artwork from new concepts to developments.
- Collaborating ideals with Trim Graphic Manager on improving productivity.
- Responsibility includes management of the designs of not only trim/hardware but jewelry, footwear, accessories, belts, small leather goods, product design, all gift giving and promotional events design development for all five distinct brands.

### **EDUCATIONS**

- 2020 Present, University of California Davis, Division of Continuing Professional Education
- 2017 2018, Easy Truck Rental for CDL, Commercial Driving License
- 2004 2006, Westwood College, Bachelor of Science in Visual Communications
- 2002 2004, Westwood College, Associate Degree in Graphic Design